hungrybags.com 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy â€“ HungryBags

**Private Policy of Hungry Bags, a part of Travel Kamp Pvt. Ltd.**

Hungry Bags an online Travel Portal that provides information on various cities of the world and recommend hotels, vacation Rentals, travel packages, cruises etc through visitors opinion. Our Web site is part of the Travel Kamp Pvt. Ltd. and the same is based out of New Delhi India.  

We believe in our visitors for giving their opinion / views on any subject and the same is not biased. We are taking all measures to ensure that all the personal information shared by our visitor shall remains confidential. We recommend our visitors that before submitting they submit their personal information on our Web site, please read this Policy carefully to learn about our privacy practices. Please read this private policy of www.hungrybags.com, we assume that you are accepting the practices described herein.

**Privacy Policy**  
Once a visitor provides his personal information like name, email id, Phone number, Address , User Id & Passwords, or any other travel related information, the same is stored in our database and the is protected at our end and we take all measure to ensure that the information is not disclosed to any third party who is not affiliated with Hungry Bags. Only Authorized employees of Hungry Bags are allowed to manage such personal information and the same is protected through number of firewalls to stop leakage of the same. Although the visitor has option not to provide all or any of the information to us, but some general information is required in order for you to enjoy the benefits of being a registered member. Visitors of www.hungrybags.com will have an option to provide contact information of their friends & family on our Web site. It is recommended that visitor should take the consent of friends & Family before providing the same to www.hungrybags.com.

Hungry Bags also obtain both personal and non-personal information of people around the world from their partners and affiliated. In case you don't want us to write you, you can always opt for unsubscribe option and we will not use that information again. Although the same will remain idle in our database.

Hungry Bags automatically pulls out some information about your computer when you browse www.hungrybags.com from your computer i.e., we procure session data, that includes your IP address, Web browser software. Through this private policy, Hungry Bags assume that it has sole rights to collect information about your online activity on www.hungrybags.com, such as content viewed and pages visited. The information collected is just to understand the interests of our users and help them by giving better services by adding new features on the page visited. The same information helps us tying up with hotels, Airlines and other places to procure better deals for you directly or by way of advertisement.

Hungry Bags has a policy not to disclose visitors personal information with any third parties who are not affiliated with us. Although if any link on www.hungrybags.com takes you to another website then we recommend you to see the private policy of that particular website too.

**Data protection Rules of Various Countries**  
Although Hungry Bags assure all the visitors that data is protected and all information shall remain confidential but if you are visiting www.hungrybags.com from outside India, please be aware that the data protection laws of India might not be the same as in your country. At the same time, please be assured that Hungry Bags takes all possible measure and uses internal firewalls to ensure that your privacy / Data is protected. 

**Children's private Policy**  
www.hungrybags.com can be accessed by visitors in general in any part of the world at the same time it does not offer services to children under the age of 13 years. If any Visitor with an age less than 13 years becomes our member, we generally delete or destroy such information as soon as we come to know of the same fact.

**Changes to Private Policy**  
Hungry Bags, a part of Travel Kamp Pvt Ltd reserves sole rights to add / modify the private policy at any time. Although we update our visitors such changes through emails but we still recommend visitors of our site to read private policy periodically before using the site. In case of any information on data protection, You can always write to us at:  
We would be glad to help you as soon as possible.
